hey guys don't forget to subscribe and
大家别忘了订阅
turn on your notifications mega what's
超级大地打开通知
wrong why are you so sad
错，你为什么这么难过
it was that you know what my mom just
那是你知道我妈妈只是
got a new boyfriend I don't know how I'm
有一个新男朋友，我不知道我怎么了
like worried for her she's not that
喜欢为她担心，她不是那样的人
young
年轻
oh come on you just missed your dad I
哦，拜托，你只是想念你爸爸
want to go over this class seriously
想认真上这节课
where is the teacher hi class I'll be
我要去的老师好吗？
offended - for today my name is mr.
得罪了-今天我的名字是先生。
Buckner dr. Hoffman is out sick today so
巴克纳博士霍夫曼今天病了，所以
he had me come in and teach the class
他让我进来教课
[Music]
[音乐]
[Applause]
[掌声]
hey I said you know let's go around the
嘿，我说你知道我们去吧
class and learn about each other yes I
上课，互相了解是的，我
am a go week SPE and you can take the
是一周的SPE，您可以参加
bottom on typical it's class time can
最典型的是上课时间可以
you be quiet mr. Buckner I'm class Ella
你安静点。 Buckner我在Ella上课
Victorian if you need anything at all
维多利亚时代，如果您什么都需要
you just let me know
你只是让我知道
Thank You Josie I'll see you after class
谢谢乔茜，我下课后见
he's gonna be ours and knows you're so
他会成为我们的，并且知道你是如此
right it's on Center Lee competition
正确，这是在李中锋比赛中
when I've already won vivid
当我已经赢得生动时
you got teacher zoned okay fine let's
你把老师划好了，让我们
make a bet the first one to get him to
第一个下注让他参加
kiss you on the cheek hey guys
在脸颊上亲你
okay sorry I'm late alright so the rules
好的，抱歉，我迟到了，所以规则
are as follows there are no rules
如下没有规则
you owe me you get all of this
你欠我你所有的一切
Oh
哦
[Music]
[音乐]
[Applause]
[掌声]
you okay oh yes no okay well let's go
你好吧，哦，是的，不好吧，走吧
let's play ball I don't know I meet up
让我们打球，我不认识我
all this hot teacher thing and me and
所有这些热门老师的事情，我和
Chelsea just gets me like stressed out
切尔西让我感到压力重重
and yeah I just gotta be more aggressive
是的，我只是要更具侵略性
don't ya can you punch her in the face I
不，你能打我一拳吗
will punch her in the face
会打她的脸
thank you hey Leila that's cool I could
谢谢，嘿，莱拉，很酷，我可以
show you around
带你四处看看
I gotta tackle a little but maybe after
我要解决一点，但也许之后
lunch okay hey Lilly maybe a minute talk
午餐好吧，礼来，也许一分钟的谈话
yes oh okay cool I've heard so much
是的，很好，我听到的很多
about you and I did want to come over
关于你，我确实想过来
and introduce myself and you know that
自我介绍，你知道
one may I yeah come here okay no I'm
我可以，是的，来这里好吧，不，我是
we're practically family now so wait I'm
我们现在几乎是一家人了，等等我
dating your mom it's been going so great
和你妈妈约会真是太好了
you're the guy he's a gun
你是他是枪的家伙
it's been a blast are you okay
爆炸了，你还好吗
what's going on yo are you okay this
怎么回事哟，你还好吗
there's a dream sorry I just have these
有一个梦，对不起，我只有这些
little dreams in my hands I okay yeah
我手上有个小小的梦想
totally understandable yeah there's my
完全可以理解的是
mom
妈妈
hey sexy honey thank you guys so much
嘿，性感宝贝，非常感谢你们
for watching don't forget to Like
看着别忘了喜欢
comment and check out my link for image
评论并查看我的图像链接
[Music]
[音乐]